Hello Gas Welcome to Video Stock Market
Friends ICICI Lombard General
Insurance has presented its September quarter
financial results which we will
discuss in today's video. If you
look here, the quarter and half year
results have been presented and the company has
also declared a dividend
which will be an interest dividend of Rs 4.5 per
equity share which
is an affected dividend which is 45% of the face value of the
company. The record of which has been
kept on 28 October 2022. So now we
move on to the company's financial
results which are given in gas numbers legs.
If you look at the income here, the
company has generated an income of Rs 4489 crore, sorry Rs 199 crore,
whereas in the previous quarter an
income of Rs 3978 crore was generated and
in the September 21 quarter an income of Rs 38 crore was
generated. So this time the income which is
quarter on quarter and this year
in comparison to both the income there has been a very
good growth.  Similarly, if we
talk about expenses, then if you look at the expenses here, then
this time the
expenses that have come out can be seen, it is an
expense of 398 crores, which was an
expense of 361 crores in the previous quarter and in the September 21
quarter it was an expense of 3551 crores,
so the expenses of the company can also be seen here,
quarter on quarter around,
according to every income, there is an
increase in the expense,
now if we talk about the profit of the company here, the profit
of the company which came out this time,
profit after tax 500,
if we see here, then a
profit of 50090 crores has been generated here,
whereas in the previous quarter there was a
profit of ₹349 crores and in
September 21, a profit of 446 crores was
generated, so along with the income of the company, there
is also growth in the profit of the company, which
means
overall if we look at the financial result of the company, it is a
very strong financial result.  is
getting very strong
results, this time the company has also presented apps
here, if you see then the
company has seen a growth of 12.03 from apps here, which is excellent growth
from the last quarter and from last year,
now if
seen here then the company has
seen a good performance, the company has given a very good
performance which
can be said that here
marine health
including personal accident
generates revenue from all these, hence the
revenue of the company is generated from all types
because you can see the data here on the screen,
which is a good result
presented by the company this time, so now we are
renting the video here, if you have any
doubt then ask in the comment box, we will meet
in the next video, tick